

# MEDINA DACIĆ FUKELJ

Software Developer

# About Me

I am a full-stack developer with almost 5 years of experience in various technologies and frameworks.

I'm detail oriented, hard working and out of a box thinker. I'm interested only in remote contract jobs (no reallocation).

#### https://www.linkedin.com/in/medinadacic/



medina.daca@gmail.com



Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

### LANGUAGE

- English (professional)
- Bosnian (native)

#### **EXPERTISE**

- Web development
- Angular
- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS
- C#
- Git
- Agile/Scrum

### **EXPERIENCE**

Softray Solutions, Sarajevo Dec 2021 - Present (2y 7m)

I'm working as a software developer full-time job.

I mostly work with Angular, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, and C#. We use SCRUM. I also had the opportunity to work as a Mentor for new employees.

Authority Partners, Sarajevo Oct 2019 - Nov 2021 (2y 2m)

Worked as full-stack software engineer full-time job. I worked with different technologies and frameworks such as .NET, Angular, Azure, SSRS, Entity framework, Databases, SSMS, Power Bi... We used SCRUM.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **University of Sarajevo**

Faculty of Electrical engineering, Computer Science 2015-2019

#### High school of Economics in Sarajevo

High School Diploma, Economics 2011-2015

# **PROJECTS**

https://github.com/Dacili/FE-projects

My Github account: https://github.com/Dacili